whois.com.au 2019-05-12

# 

## Sharing

Disclosure of Customer Information 

Vodien will not disclose its customers' personal information with third parties, with the exception of the following reasons: 

  * To provide service to the registered account user 
  * To cooporate with law enforcement agencies via legal processes such as current judicial proceedings, court orders and warrants that Vodien determines in its sole discretion to be legitimate and compliable 
  * To safeguard the legitimate interests of Vodien and its customers 

In any event, whereby Vodien is obliged to disclose customer data in adherence to the served legal process(es), Vodien may disclose any forms of User Information to the respective Law Enforcement Agency without prior consent or notification to the customer. Any interactions between Vodien and the Officials will not be divulged, in order to protect Vodien's legal interests. 

Business Transitions 

In the event Vodien Internet Solutions goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

Choice/Opt-out 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by sending us an email at [marketing@vodien.com](mailto:marketing@vodien.com). We also offer an opt-out mechanism on the newsletter subscription confirmation email. Alternatively, the user may contact us at 1300 863 436 to opt-out. 

Users of our site are always notified when their information is being collected by any outside parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether or not they should proceed with services that require an outside party. 

Links 

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Vodien Internet Solutions, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

Surveys & Contests 

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as postal code). Contact information will be shared with the contest/survey sponsors and used to notify the winners and award prizes. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums 

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Advertisements via Third-Party Vendors 

  * Third-party vendors, including Google, show your ads on sites on the internet. 
  * Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to your website. 
  * Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting the [Google advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively you can point users to opt out of a third party vendor’s use of cookies by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative opt out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information 

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as postal code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users' personally identifiable information. This can be done by emailing our Customer Support at [support@vodien.com](mailto:support@vodien.com). 

Notification of Changes 

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

Contact Information 

Questions regarding this privacy policy may be directed to [contact@vodien.com](mailto:contact@vodien.com). 

_The above stated Privacy Policy is correct as of 6th of April 2018._
